### GRANT MCINTYRE

https://grants-portfolio.web.app /index.html

#### SKILLS

- Proven Leader
- Relationship building and maintaining
- Strong Communicator
- Problem Solving
- Personable, Sense of humour
- Determined
- Ambitious
- Resilient
- TECHNOLOGY
- Software Development HTML5,
  CSS3, Javascript, React, Git, Yarn,
  API's, Authentication and
  Authorization, Unit Testing
- Front-end Libraries and
  Frameworks SASS, Bootstrap
  Materialize
- Back-end Development -Firebase. Node.is
- Githuh
- Agile

# HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

- Sports enthusiast, namely Football and Golf
- Music &Theatre
- Reading
- Fitness
- Cooking, food & drink

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Determined and ambitious with a willingness to learn and to constantly improve. Have spent 5 years working as a performer in a unique and fiercely competitive industry; looking to transfer the skills developed and engendered there into the technology sector and to expand on the skills and grounding the \_nology Software Development course has engineered. This technological education and experience combined with that of my previous career make me suitable for a role where communication and relationships lie at the heart.

#### EDUCATION

### 12 WEEK INTENSIVE SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT COURSE

\_nology (2020)

#### Remote

- Taught entirely remotely, engineering hands-on experience of coding in multiple programming languages, frameworks and tools.
- Primarily Front-end focussed but ventured into Back-end too with a commitment to adhering to industry standard best practices.
- The course ranged from codealongs with coaches to working as part of a development team in an Agile environment on a real client project with a client based in San Francisco, USA.
- Project managed and led a sprint in this Agile environment.

#### BACHELOR OF ARTS

The Guildford School of Acting (2012–15)

- Advanced communication and presentational skills
- Self discipline
- Ambition
- Resilience

#### EXPERIENCE

#### ACTOR IN CAST

'Beautiful; The Carole King Musical' Mark Rubinstein Ltd UK & Ireland Theatre Tour November 2019 - March 2020 & Aug 2017-Jul 2018

## PERFORMER IN 4 PIECE GUEST ENTERTAINER ACT

The Other Guys UK Ltd Worldwide, Celebrity and NCL Cruise Lines December 2018 - November 2019

#### DIRECTOR & ACTOR

The Fingask Follies Perth, Scotland & Touring April 2019 - June 2019 & Mar-Jun 2017

#### ACTOR IN CAST

'The Sessions Live! - The Beatles at Abbey Road' Soundstage Theatre Corp UK & Ireland Arena Tour March 2016 - July 2016